background-kid.com 2015-05-26

# Privacy Policy

### _Privacy Policy_

####  Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available in our footer and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. Log files are maintained and analysed of all requests for files on this website’s web servers. Log files do not capture personal information but do capture the user’s IP address, which is automatically recognised by our web servers. This website does not store any information that would, on its own, allow us to identify individual users of this service without their permission. Any cookies that may be used by this website are used either solely on a per session basis or to maintain user preferences. Cookies are not shared with any third parties. 

Third Parties 

  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website.
  * Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users that are based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites across the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of using the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/). (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies for interest-based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).)

Home Home \- Search \- About \- Links \- Privacy Policy \- Contact Us
